{
    "subject": "resource/Sagina_Mahato",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Films_based_on_actual_events",
    "human_readable": "Sagina Mahato is subject to Films based on actual events.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9840565919876099,
            "question": "Are the films featuring Sagina Mahato based on real events?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9791127443313599,
            "question": "Does Sagina Mahato conduct research for her roles in films based on actual events?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9507739543914795,
            "question": "Does Sagina Mahato act in other genres besides films based on actual events?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8572888374328613,
            "question": "Are there any specific historical events depicted in Sagina Mahato's films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.852368950843811,
            "question": "How does Sagina Mahato portray real-life events in her films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.786820650100708,
            "question": "What are the themes explored in Sagina Mahato's films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7083753347396851,
            "question": "What kind of films does Sagina Mahato appear in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6648312211036682,
            "question": "Can you name some films starring Sagina Mahato?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5047023296356201,
            "question": "What is Sagina Mahato known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4438464939594269,
            "question": "What is the impact of Sagina Mahato's acting on viewers?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sagina Mahato is subject to Films based on actual events.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6387_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Sagina Mahato known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6387_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name some films starring Sagina Mahato?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6387_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of films does Sagina Mahato appear in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6387_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6387_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6387_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6387_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6387_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6387_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6387_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6387_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6387_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6387_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6387_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the film \"Sagina Mahato\" and its remake, indicating that it was based on a true story involving labor unrest in the tea estates of Darjeeling during the early 1940s. This supports the statement that the film is subject to \"Films based on actual events.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}